slickpic.com 2019-03-01

# Privacy Policy - SlickPic

## SlickPic Privacy Policy

SlickPic recognizes that privacy is important.  Ensuring your privacy is taken very seriously.  Our privacy policy applies to all of the products, services offered by SlickPic.  By using our site, you consent to the terms in this privacy policy. 

SlickPic's purpose is to enable its customers to upload and share photos and videos.  We provide tools and the SlickPic service to enable our customers to share photos, videos and other metadata on SlickPic website and communicate with other users. 

SlickPic enables sharing photos and videos with both authenticated and anonymous viewers over the Internet, while providing you with privacy settings that restrict other users from accessing your information.  Our network architecture and your privacy settings allow you to make informed choices about who has access to your information. 

Our primary responsibility is to our customers, who in turn have relationships with their viewers.  This privacy policy covers both our customers and the viewers of our customer’s photos, videos and other information. 

## Security and Privacy Information for SlickPic Customers

You can change your security and privacy settings at any time.  You are in control of your SlickPic website and control how much security to impose. You decide which albums to publish and what photos and videos to include.  You decide whether your SlickPic site is open to the public, locked down with a password, or unlisted.  SlickPic’s role is to enable you to publish your photos and videos (coming soon) and enable you to collect comments and other data from your viewers. 

## What Information Does SlickPic Collect?

When you visit our SlickPic web pages, you provide us with four types of information: 

  * personal information you knowingly choose to disclose
  * system usage information regarding your photo and video albums
  * website use and technical support information

When you register and create an account with SlickPic, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your email address.  When you purchase a subscription or other photo merchandise products or services, you provide your credit card and other personal or preference information. 

When you create albums, we store the digital images you give us, the album descriptions and other information you enter to customize your albums.  We also log certain usage information on our servers as you create and manage your photos and videos. 

When you request support we may collect information about the nature of your problem and we may log additional information about system usage to try to help you. 

When you enter SlickPic, we collect your browser type, IP address, stream data and HTTP protocol elements.  This information is gathered for all SlickPic visitors.  In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies".  A cookie is a piece of data stored on your computer tied to information about the user.  We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in.  These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser.  To make it easier for you to login when you return to SlickPic, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID, but not your password.  If you want to disable this convenience feature, you can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser. 

When you use SlickPic, you create your personal profile, form relationships, upload photos and/or videos (User Content), comment on albums, form groups,  and transmit information through various channels.  We collect this information so we can provide you the service and offer personalized features.  In most cases, we retain it so, for example, you can easily see your friend or family member list, or view prior messages you have sent. 

When you use our invitation feature to connect to a friend or family member about your site, we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your friend or family member’s name and email address.  We will automatically send your friend or family member an email inviting him or her to visit the site and inviting them to join SlickPic.  We store this information to send this invitation, to register a friend or family member connection if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of sharing invitations.  Your friend or family member may contact us at [abuse@SlickPic.com](mailto:abuse@SlickPic.com) to request that we remove this information from our database. 

You post User Content (as defined in the SlickPic Terms of Use) on the site at your own risk.  Although you control settings for privacy options that limit access to your pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable.  We cannot control the actions of other users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information.  Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on the site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.  We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the site.  You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content. 

Any personal information in your public profile, public albums and blogs, public comments, public photos will be accessible by other SlickPic users and website guests who may view your profile and your public page information and comment on any of your public photos and videos, add themselves to your list of followers, and send you messages. Users can see the list of viewers who voted for user, added users photo as a favorite(s) and who followed user. 

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on SlickPic is a violation of the SlickPic Terms of Use and should be reported to [abuse@SlickPic.com](mailto:abuse@SlickPic.%C2%A0com). 

## How Do You Protect My Information?

When you access your personal information we implement a variety of security measures to ensure the safety of your personal information. 

These security measures might include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information, SSL (Secure Sockets Layer)  technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely or PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities. 

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. 

## What Are Public, Private and Unlisted Settings?

SlickPic users can designate their Albums and Collections as Public, Private or Unlisted. 

Use the Public privacy setting to showcase your photos to everyone. Make your albums and collections visible to your friends, family and community. This is the current default setting for photos unless you change it.  
Set your albums to Public to make them viewable to anyone who has the album's URL. Public albums are searchable on the web and visible on the Gallery, Home, Community Gallery and other similar pages on both computers and mobile devices. Public Photos and Albums can be shared via social networks and email. Viewers can Vote, Like, Comment and add to their favorite list. Photos in Public albums may be downloaded using right click unless you check Disable Right Click Saves in the Enhanced Privacy menu. Viewers can contact authors if the author has authorized this function in Account Preferences. 

Use the Unlisted privacy setting to control who will see your albums and collections. Unlisted albums aren't listed on your SlickPic gallery home page, aren't included in search engines, and aren't visible on the Community pages. Unlisted albums have to be shared before anyone could view them.  
Shared Unlisted albums include a unique key in the URL web address, a combination of letters and numbers that make the address difficult to guess.  
Unlisted is not the same as Private. People can still get access to the unlisted album that you've shared with friends, for example if your friend will forward the encrypted URL web address to somebody else, publish it on the web, or just leave the album open on the public computer. Additionally, Internet browsers keep browsing history.  
Password Protect your album if you want more privacy. You can do it in Album Preferences. 

Use the Private setting if you are not ready to share your photos. You will be able to view your photos when logged in but no other viewers will see them. Private albums are for personal use only. They can not be shared. To share an album please use either the Public or Unlisted privacy option. 

SlickPic users can modify their Album and Collection settings using either the menu next to an existing individual Album or Collection or set a default for new Albums or Collections via the Account menu. 

## Privacy Options For Bio

You can set your Bio to Visible or Hidden.  To make your bio Visible, uncheck the Hide bio box, which will allow other users to see your Bio in galleries and searches.  Keep the box checked if you do not want other users to view or search your Bio. 

You may designate a Real Name, Screen Name or Business Name for your Bio.  If you set your Bio to Visible your designated name is searchable on our site.  If you are using your Real Name, it is also searchable on the site. 

To modify your Account Settings please go to your Account page and review your information in the My Bio Page menu tab. 

## Security of Sensitive Information

SlickPic takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information.  When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card numbers or your password), we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).  Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send private information to us by email or instant messaging services.  If you have any questions about the security of SlickPic Web Site, please contact us at info@SlickPic.com.  SlickPic utilizes third party online storage vendors to store photo and video sharing data and relies on the security of those vendors to keep data secure. 

## How Does SlickPic Use My Information?

When you register with SlickPic, you create your own profile and privacy settings.  Your profile information, as well as your name, email and photo, are displayed to people in the relationships specified in your privacy settings to enable you to connect with people on SlickPic.  We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by SlickPic that we think you may find valuable. 

Profile information is used by SlickPic primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access the service, and to be presented to others permitted to view that information by your privacy settings.  In some cases where your privacy settings permit it (e. g. , posting comments to your albums), other SlickPic users and visitors may be able to supplement your albums. 

Bio information you provided about yourself will be available for public to see. 

SlickPic may send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service.  For instance, if a friend sends you a new album notification message or someone posts comments on your album, you may receive an email alerting you to that fact. 

We use logged diagnostic information to fix bugs and track down problems.  In the course of customer support, we may look at system logs to try to understand what you were doing when you had a problem. 

When you ask us a question via Ask Us/Feedback button, we collect information sent to us by your computer or other access device. The information sent to us includes your name and email address where we need to respond, your membership level and date of sign up, your computer IP address, device identifiers, the type of browser and operating system you’re using, and other information. 

We utilize system usage information and logged diagnostic information to improve our service.  We also look at aggregate demographic information to try to understand who are customers are and to guide future product development. 

SlickPic and its agents use transmission data and HTTP protocol elements for the following purposes: 

  * Website and system administration. 
  * Research and development. 
  * Anonymous user analysis. 
  * Anonymous user profiling and decision-making. 
  * To provide statistics to album owners on the use of their albums. 

## Do You Share Information with Third Parties?

SlickPic does not provide contact information to third party marketers without your permission.  We do not share, sell, or rent your email address to third parties.  We share your information with third parties only in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is 1) reasonably necessary to offer the service, 2) legally required or, 3) permitted by you. For example:  

  * Your news feed may aggregate the information you provide and make it available to your friends and network members according to your privacy settings.  You may set your preferences for your news feed in your SlickPic privacy settings on your SlickPic home page.   
SlickPic offers user controls to block access to open site information by third party search engine "crawlers" (e. g.  Google, Yahoo, etc.).  Generally,  search engines respect markup on pages that directs search engines to exclude the site content, but respecting such conventions is voluntary on the part of the search engines. 

  * Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to SlickPic-specified purposes.  We may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the services we offer.  Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the service at a co-location or other facility for servers, to send out email updates about SlickPic, to process and fulfill print and other photo services, to remove repetitive information from our user lists or to process payments for products or services.  In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities. 

  * We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws.  We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards.  Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the SlickPic service or using the SlickPic name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm.  This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies. 

  * If the ownership of all or substantially all of the SlickPic business were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations.  In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy. 

When you use SlickPic, certain information you post or share with third parties (e. g. , a friend or family member), such as personal information, comments, messages, photos, videos, or other information, may be shared with other users in accordance with the privacy settings you select.  All such sharing of information is done at your own risk.  Please be aware that if you disclose personal information in your profile or when posting comments, messages, photos, videos, or other items, this information may become publicly available. 

## What About Links?

SlickPic may contain links to other websites.  We do not review or monitor any websites linked from SlickPic and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of any such linked web sites.  We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.  This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by SlickPic. 

## Can I Modify or Delete My Personal Information?

Access and control over most personal information on SlickPic is readily available through your Account Settings options.  SlickPic users can modify or delete any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account.  Information will be updated immediately.  If you want to deactivate your SlickPic account, you may do so by contacting SlickPic via email (info@slickpic.com).  Removed information may persist in backup copies and cached or archived pages for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to users of SlickPic. 

When you make use of the communication features of the service to share information with other individuals on SlickPic,  (e. g. , sending a personal message or invitation to another SlickPic user, or applying comments on SlickPic users’ albums) you generally cannot remove such communications. 

## Information for Viewers

You don't have to register for an account to view photos and videos posted on SlickPic albums by customers.  As a viewer, you may comment on albums and videos; these comments can be seen by anyone who visits the albums or videos. 

If you view a SlickPic website controlled by one of our customers, we may collect certain information from you.  Each SlickPic customer also has access to some of the data we collect.  For example, visitor reports and logs of comments left by viewers are available to SlickPic customers. 

SlickPic does not control what its customers do with the data we share.  SlickPic expects and requires its customers to abide by SlickPic’s Terms of Use.  We will terminate a customer’s account if we become aware that a SlickPic customer has violated our terms of service. 

## E-mail Communications

SlickPic is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the "Sharing Your Information" section below. SlickPic may send out e-mails with SlickPic-related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions. You may also receive notification e-mails from SlickPic, which inform you of actions (e.g. friend requests) that have been performed on the site. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, please visit the Communications Settings in Account menu and uncheck the unwanted e-mail messages. However, please note that in all cases you will continue to receive all system and administrative emails: newsletters, alerts, important messages from us. 

## Analytics

SlickPic uses Google Analytics service to help analyze and understand how our site and mobile applications are used, so that we can make SlickPic products more interesting to you. These tools capture data about how individual users are using our site and mobile applications. This includes event logs, device type and device configuration settings such as language, crash data and other data but never personal information. These third-party services treat the analytics data in accordance with this privacy policy and SlickPic does not disclose your personal information to any third parties through our use of these services. 

## Keeping Information Secure

Your SlickPic account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. Protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer. Your name and email address are stored in encrypted format.   
Only employees who need personal information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to it. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices. 

## Ways to Control Display and Use of Your Information

  * As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, but then you may be unable to use certain features on our website.
  * By visiting your User Profile, you can correct, amend, add or delete personal information on our website.
  * If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, please visit the Communications Settings in Account menu and uncheck the unwanted e-mail messages. However, please note that in all cases you will continue to receive all system and administrative emails: newsletters, alerts, important messages from us.
  * As explained earlier, the "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. Please note, however, that if your browser does not accept cookies, some site functionality might become unusable.

## Information modification or Deletion

You have the right at any time to request information about what personal data we process about you and to demand correction, deletion and/or restriction of your personal data stored by us. For your security, we will ask you to verify your details in the event of such a request or change. Please contact us at: https://support.slickpic.com 

## Your California Privacy Rights

California law permits residents of California to request certain details about how their information is shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please contact us at support@slickpic.com 

## SlickPic Policies on Cookies

SLICKPIC uses cookies (small text files placed on your device) and similar technologies to provide our website and online services and to help collect data. The text in a cookie often consists of a string of numbers and letters that uniquely identifies your computer, but it can contain other information as well. 

## Our Use of Cookies and Similar Technologies

SLICKPIC uses cookies and similar technologies for several purposes, depending on the product, including: 

  * Storing your Preferences and Settings. Settings that enable our products to operate correctly or that maintain your preferences over time may be stored on your device. For example, if you enter your city or postal code to get nearby groups or events on the SLICKPIC website, we may store that data in a cookie so that you will see the relevant local information when you return to the site. We also save preferences, such as language, browser and time zone, so those do not have to be reset each time you return to the site.
  * Sign-in and Authentication. When you sign into a website using your personal SLICKPIC account, we store a unique ID number, and the time you signed in, in an encrypted cookie on your device. This cookie allows you to move from page to page within the site without having to sign in again on each page. You can also save your sign- in information so you do not have to sign in each time you return to the site.
  * Security. We use cookies to detect fraud and abuse of our websites and services.
  * Storing Information you Provide to a Website. When you provide information: submit comments, groups, events and other information, we store the data in a cookie to remember the information you have added.
  * Social Media. Some of our websites include social media cookies, including those that enable users who are logged in to the social media service to share content via that service.
  * Feedback. SLICKPIC uses cookies to enable you to provide feedback and report malfunctions on a website.
  * Interest-Based Content. SLICKPIC uses cookies to collect data about your online activity and identify your interests so that we can provide content or advertising that is most relevant to you.
  * Showing Content. SLICKPIC uses cookies to record how many visitors have clicked on a content or advertisement and to record what you have seen so you don’t see the same one repeatedly.
  * Analytics. In order to provide our products, we use cookies and other identifiers to gather usage and performance data. For example, we use cookies to count the number of unique visitors to a web page or service and to develop other statistics about the operations of our products. This includes cookies from SLICKPIC and from third-party analytics providers.
  * Performance. SLICKPIC uses cookies for load balancing to ensure that websites remain up and running.

Cookies that to collect information for analytics purposes. In addition to the cookies SLICKPIC sets when you visit our websites, third parties may also set cookies when you visit SLICKPIC site. In some cases, that is because we have hired the third party to provide services on our behalf, such as site analytics. In other cases, it is because our web pages contain content or ads from third parties, such as videos, news content or ads delivered by other ad networks. Because your browser connects to those third parties' web servers to retrieve that content, those third parties are able to set or read their own cookies on your device and may collect information about your online activities across websites or online services. 

## How to Control Cookies

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but provide controls that allow you to block or delete them. For example, in Internet Explorer or Microsoft Edge, you can block or delete cookies by clicking Settings → Privacy → Cookies. Instructions for blocking or deleting cookies in other browsers may be available in each browser's privacy or help documentation. Certain features of SLICKPIC products depend on cookies. Please be aware that if you choose to block cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use those features, and preferences that are dependent on cookies may be lost. If you choose to delete cookies, settings and preferences controlled by those cookies, including advertising preferences, will be deleted and may need to be recreated. 

## Our Use of Web Beacons and Analytics Services

SLICKPIC web pages may contain electronic images known as web beacons (also called single- pixel gifs) that we use to help deliver cookies on our website and count users who have visited this website. We also include web beacons in our promotional email messages or newsletters to determine whether you open and act on them. SLICKPIC products often contain web beacons or similar technologies from third-party analytics providers, which help us compile aggregated statistics about the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns or other operations. These technologies enable the analytics providers to set or read their own cookies or other identifiers on your device, through which they can collect information about your online activities across applications, websites or other products. However, we prohibit these analytics providers from using web beacons on our sites to collect or access information that directly identifies you (such as your name or email address). 

## Other Similar Technologies

In addition to standard cookies and web beacons, our products can also use other similar technologies to store and read data files on your computer. This is typically done to maintain your preferences or to improve speed and performance by storing certain files locally. But, like standard cookies, these technologies can also be used to store a unique identifier for your computer, which can then be used to track behavior. These technologies include Local Shared Objects (or "Flash cookies”). Local Shared Objects or "Flash cookies." Web sites that use Adobe Flash technologies can use Local Shared Objects or "Flash cookies" to store data on your computer. To manage or block Flash cookies, go to [www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html](https://www.slickpic.com/www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html). 

## Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions

Your use of SlickPic, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy, as well as our Terms of Use and all of its dispute resolution provisions, limitation on damages and choice of law.  We encourage you to refer to our policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy.  Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.  We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time.  Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.  This policy was last modified on 9/06/2010.  

## CAN-SPAM Compliance

SlickPic has taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information. 

## Contacting SlickPic

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at [info@SlickPic.com](mailto:info@SlickPic.com)

## Security

SlickPic takes reasonable measures to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Data Retention We store the information we collect about you for as long as is necessary for the purpose(s) for which we originally collected it. We may retain certain information for legitimate business purposes or as required by law. Data Transfers To provide the Services, we may transfer your information to SlickPic servers in the United States or other countries. When we transfer information from the European Economic Area (“EEA”) to countries that have not been deemed to provide an adequate level of protection, we employ data processing agreements based on the Standard Contractual Clauses to help ensure that your data is protected wherever it is transferred. 

If you are a resident of the EEA, you have certain rights and protections under the law regarding the processing of your personal information. 

## Legal Basis for Processing

If you are a resident of the EEA, when we process your personal data we will only do so in the following situations: 

  * We need to use your personal information to perform our responsibilities under our contract with you (e.g., processing payments for and providing the services you have requested).
  * We have a legitimate interest in processing your personal data. For example, we may process your personal data to send you marketing communications, to communicate with you about changes to our services, and to provide, secure, and improve our services.

## Data Subject Requests

If you are a resident of the EEA, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, erased, or transferred. You may also have the right to object to, or request that we restrict, certain processing. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, you can log into your account and use the settings and features explained above or you may contact us as indicated below. 

## Questions or Complaints

If you are a resident of the EEA and have a concern about our processing of personal information that we are not able to resolve, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the data privacy authority where you reside. For contact details of your local Data Protection Authority, please see: http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/article-29/structure/data-protection- authorities/index_en.htm.
